so
good afternoon everyone i am adrika and
now
uh it's finally time for our next
question
question number four of the day so
now without uh you know without
any further due let's just begin with
our question
so the question is that
so the question is that you need to
purchase
months worth of grocery
which you will need to carry back
on your two willow you will
a keep it on the front of the two
wheeler
b take a rickshaw and go c
keep it on the back of the two wheeler
or d
hang it on the sides of the two wheeler
so i just once again repeat this
question in hindi as well
so
[Music]
so you know this was the question
that you need to purchase months worth
of grocery which you will have to carry
back
on your two-wheeler uh and in this
situation
what will you do so you know
shoot us a question
up there we can do a lot by this simple
step of
answering a small question you know so i
will just
ask you all i will request you all to uh
question jealousy answer curry uh
you know it does not take a lot of time
also
so you know it's really
[Music]
you know we are trying to make sure that
the roads become safer
and you know you can become a part of us
for this mission
so you know you can become a part of us
in this mission
you know
is
foreign
[Music]
you know you all should answer this
because it does not take a lot of time
you know just try to answer this as soon
as possible
you know this is valid for two hours
only so
uh you know the question yeah basically
how much questions say classic
so uh you know
[Music]
and what
so
so basically this is what we can uh you
know
learn from this question so i will just
once again repeat this question
uh you need to purchase months
worth of grocery which you will have to
carry back
on your two wheeler you will so
uh so you know you have a lot of grocery
and you have to carry all that back home
on your two-wheeler so in this situation
when you have a lot of grocery and you
have to carry it all
back on your two wheeler so what will
you do
a keep it on the front keep it on the
front of the two wheeler b
take a rickshaw and go c
keep it on the back of the two below or
d
hang it on the sides of the two willow
so uh you know this is our question
question number four
in total it will uh it will be our 39th
question and it is really simple to
answer
we all can draw learn a lot in this
question
and i hope that all of you were a part
of the previous questions as well
and i request you all to please answer
this question
as well as the other questions which
will be coming today
uh you know uh rosa my past five
questions and
uh
you know first of all you are becoming a
part
you know we all want to make sure that
your roots are safe
but still it is not the safest you know
still it is not
safe uh rose road crashes
and that is why humay
uh in roadska or safe banana so first of
all
benefit is that you are becoming a part
of us
the second thing is that you are
learning
you know
simply secret okay what how our behavior
should be there
on the roads so we can learn a lot
how we should be behaving on the roads
and uh and you know if we come to know
that how our behavior should be there on
the roads
it is simple that we will make the roads
safer
you know we will make the roads safer
and lesser crashes will happen
on the road and the most important one
uh is that you can win some exciting
prizes either a bike safety kit for you
and your family
or a car safety kit for uh
and
[Music]
you know you're
safe uh you know and that is why you
know i would like to
ask you all and request you all to also
involve other people as well involve
your
involve your family involve your friends
tell them about the campaign
you know two hours each question is
valid only for
uh you know it's a answer curry and you
know it's also really simple thing
okay rose every day we are having
five questions and they are coming in a
gap of two hours so after two hours
so after every two hours a new question
will be coming
so right now uh you know it is three
o'clock so the next question
uh question number five it will come
after two hours
so you know it's really simple
but
[Music]
for our own safety
you know follow and if we talk about
this
question you know we are learning how
uh you know we should deal with things
which we have to
carry on a two-wheeler like forever
if we talk about our four-wheelers we
have the boot of the car where we can
keep our things
but what about two below so
[Music]
you should always be following these
rules traffic rules road safety rules
not for the chilan but for our own safe
months
worth of grocery you will
have to carry back on your two willow
you will a keep it on keep it on the
front of the two below
bill take a rickshaw and go see
keep it on the back of the two below or
d
hang it on the sides of the two wheeler
so you know
it's really simple to answer
[Music]
and uh you know please become a part of
this
because with this we are learning
that how our behavior should be there
on the roads and the first step of uh
you know just changing anything is
awareness and we are getting awareness
from this
question uh you know uh
we are getting awareness you know we are
trying
uh
[Music]
you know the first thing which we should
so you know we have a lot of benefits by
simply answering this question
you know and we can win uh we can also
win some exciting prizes
as well so you know like this
every two hours questions will be coming
and
uh it's really simple to answer either
with the description in the link
or from our youtube or facebook page and
the results will be
announced at 10 pm at 10 pm every day we
have a
show called bluntly speaking in that
the results as well as the answers will
be announced
and uh and also uh you can see the
results
on our website as well so
thank you so much everyone uh
thank you so much everyone and uh please
do answer this question as well as the
other questions as well
you know become a part of it and bring
the change
uh you know we this is like the first
step to make
uh you know we should start by step by
step on making
our roads safer so uh you know
please do answer this awareness mildred
we can win prizes you can win prizes and
make and also make our indian roads
safer thank you so much everyone